<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">The Chronicles of Narnia</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe</string>
    <string name="article_text">The Chronicles of Narnia: The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe is a 2005 fantasy film co-written and directed by Andrew Adamson, based on the 1950 novel The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe,
        the first published and second chronological novel in C. S. Lewiss childrens epic fantasy series, The Chronicles of Narnia. It was co-produced by Walden Media and Walt Disney Pictures and distributed by Buena Vista Pictures.
        \n\n
        William Moseley, Anna Popplewell, Skandar Keynes and Georgie Henley play Peter, Susan, Edmund, and Lucy, four British children evacuated during the Blitz to the countryside, who find a wardrobe that leads to the fantasy world of Narnia.
        There they ally with the lion Aslan (voiced by Liam Neeson) against the forces of Jadis, the White Witch (Tilda Swinton).
        \n\n
        <b>Plot</b>
        \n\n
        During World War II, the Pevensie children, Peter, Susan, Edmund and Lucy, are evacuated from a London suburb to Professor Digory Kirkes country home. Mrs. Macready, the strict housekeeper, explains he is unaccustomed to hosting children.
        \n\n
        While the Pevensies play hide-and-seek, Lucy discovers a wardrobe and enters the fantasy world called Narnia. Seeing a lamppost, Lucy encounters a faun named Mr. Tumnus, who invites her to his home. He puts Lucy to sleep by playing a lullaby on his flute.
        When Lucy wakes up, she finds Tumnus grieving. He explains that Jadis, the White Witch, has cursed Narnia to eternal winter 100 years ago. If a human is encountered, they are to be brought to her. Tumnus cannot bring himself to kidnap Lucy, so he sends her home.
        When she returns to Professor Kirkes house, hardly any time has passed, and her siblings disbelieve her story.
        \n\n
        One night, Edmund follows Lucy into the wardrobe, entering Narnia. While searching for Lucy, he meets the White Witch, who claims to be queen. She offers him Turkish Delight and the prospect of becoming king if he brings his siblings to her castle. After she departs,
        Edmund and Lucy meet again and return. Lucy tells Peter and Susan what happened, but Edmund lies, to Lucys dismay. Professor Kirke suggests she is telling the truth, though they remain unconvinced.
        \n
        For more informations https://id.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Chronicles_of_Narnia:_The_Lion,_the_Witch_and_the_Wardrobe
        \n\n
        <b>Cast</b>
        \n\n
        William Moseley as Peter Pevensie, the eldest of the four Pevensie children.
        \n
        Noah Huntley as Adult Peter Pevensie, who has grown up as a king in Narnia.
        \n
        Anna Popplewell as Susan Pevensie, the second-eldest child of the four Pevensie children.
        \n
        Sophie Winkleman as Adult Susan Pevensie, who has grown up as a queen in Narnia.
        \n
        Skandar Keynes as Edmund Pevensie, the third of the four Pevensie children.
        \n
        Mark Wells as Adult Edmund Pevensie, who has grown up as a king in Narnia.
        \n
        Georgie Henley as Lucy Pevensie, the youngest of the four Pevensie children.
        \n
        Rachael Henley (Henley\'s real-life sister) as Adult Lucy Pevensie, who has grown up as a queen in Narnia.
        \n
        Liam Neeson as the voice of Aslan, the great lion who was responsible for creating Narnia.
        \n
        Tilda Swinton as the White Witch, who holds Narnia under an eternal winter without Christmas or Spring or Summer.
        \n
        James McAvoy as Mr. Tumnus, a faun who at first works for the White Witch, but befriends Lucy Pevensie and joins Aslan\'s forces.
        </string>
    <string name="add_comment">ADD COMMENT</string>
</resources>